I'm excited.
>> You have any uh impressions of the city?
You know what you're kind of walking
into? Do you know anything about Detroit
prior to signing here?
>> Um I don't know much. I would say Motor
City. Um Mottown, that's another thing.
Watching movie and stuff. Um Ford,
that's another thing. That's really all
I know about Detroit. Other than that,
I'm just a soft boy.
>> From a from a football perspective, what
kind of drew you to this opportunity
here?
>> Um just the team and I'll say the coach.
um Dan just see um the type of coaching
he is. I know um the style he is just
from media. I would love to be coached
by a person like that cuz he played the
game, he know the game and I feel like
that's the best experience being coached
by somebody who been through it.
>> How would you describe your your playing
style?
>> I would say my playing style is smart um
instinctive and say aggressive. Um you
know Connor got to do more than just be
a coverage guy. So, I feel like the
other side of that is just me being
aggressive and they're showing that part
of me.
>> When they, you know, kind of make the
pitch to you, um, you know, it's
obviously more than about dollars and
cents. So, what's the the football
outlook for you here? Do you see
yourself more in that nickel role that
you've played a lot of or is it more
versatile than that?
>> I would say it's it's more versatile
than that. I would say um, anything
that's opportunity is there, anything,
any position they need me at. I know I
play a lot of nickel coner every day now
and then but I feel like no matter what
they might I can play either position.
That's the mindset I'm going into.
>> When you're playing your best ball,
Roger, what attributes of yours you feel
like shine the most?
>> Uh like I said, I said that's part of my
playing style. I feel like what shines
the most with my size and everything,
the aggressiveness. So, um, I feel like
setting the edge, tackling, being there,
um, filling in the gaps, um, disrupting
the ball and everything. I feel like
that's my playing style and that's what
stands out the most.
>> You got anybody on this roster that you
know or close with from your past that
you were able to kind of hit up about
this process during this process?
>> I'm DT Ds. Yeah. Been with me since
Arbor.
>> What did he tell you what to expect and
just about this place? Oh, he just told
me just go as you go on lock in and it's
all great here. Just feel it. The
experience. Go out your way. It's great
here. And just
enjoy and have fun. He said more than
that, but that's come on top of my head.
>> You got a chance to play in some pretty
big games with the Rams at the end of
last season. What did that experience do
for you and maybe teach you about
yourself entering this off season? Yeah,
I feel like um that's my first time ever
playing in the playoffs. So, I feel it
was great for me. Um people always said
the game speed is different than from
the regular season and it's definitely
is I was excited just to play in that
atmosphere and I feel like having that
experience that can help you at a lot of
ways knowing how the game develop and
how people attack you when it come down
to the wire. So, I feel like it was
great for me um to experience that and I
look forward to experience that more
even more past that I would say. Did
that impact the sort of teams that you
were seeking this off season having had
a chance to play for a winning team? Did
did that go into the way you um
considered teams this offseason?
>> Yeah, most definitely. Um you know, I
want to be part of something that that's
a winning winning culture and I feel
like that's the vibe here. Um you know,
the last time when I played against
them, it did not look good. So, I kind
of want to be on that side of it this
time. Um yeah, you just saying that
style. Um, I respect how this program
had built up and how it made it known
and made a name for itself. So, I feel
like I'm happy to be a part of that.
>> What's your favorite thing about
football?
>> Favorite thing about football is just
having opportunity to compete, you know,
playing this game since we love playing
this game since we were kids. Um, it's a
kids game. We just play from ransom
money, you know. So, I feel like at the
end of the day, I'm just being a little
kid playing on NFL. you did mention the
the 2024 game and didn't go Tennessee's
way that day, but you know what what did
you learn about or what do you ever
learn about an opponent just from from
playing them
that day?
>> Um, you know, I would say start off with
the quarterback Jared. I mean, he was
the guy. He kept the offense going much
respect for him. He had guys,
playmakers,
everybody around him, the defense, I
would say that was a lot. They had 10
dozen. so many ways. I I can't even just
say one person. But I know it started
with him just being the leader he is and
watching how it was a little little
thuggy at first, little there, but as
the game got on, it was over with. And I
know it was because of him and his drive
and his leadership. So seeing that and
going against them, you could just
experience and see what type of play
style they had. So that's why I'm just
excited just to practice with them and
just be their teammate. Speaking of from
beyond just a football standpoint, like
you got traded last year. Just like how
did you learn to adjust to a new team on
the fly like that and just what did you
take just from that unpredictable kind
of experience moving around like that?
>> Yeah, I feel like it was part of the
game. It's part of um you know football
say if a guy get hurt you have to be up.
You have to adjust and I feel like that
was good for me. I adjusted right away
into playing system knowing their their
defensive schemes and everything. And I
just look at it as it as it is now going
into this year. um offseason do exactly
the same thing. Play that style,
adjustment, the playing type, the
playbook, all that. So, I feel like it's
not going to be nothing new to me. It's
just day one learning and I feel like I
got the right coaches for that.
>> We do have to ask about the baked beans.
>> Is it still is this still a ritual for
you pregame? How did this come about?
You know, this is one of the first
things we saw when we were all
>> Yeah. Um I I don't do it as much as I
used to. I would say um I got to I got
to think smarter, you know, got to focus
on my diet. It catching up to me a
little bit. But um always there. No, no
doubt. Always. They cooking baked beans
in there. I'm looking directly with a
sugar. I'm always eat that no matter
what. But it's a little smarter. I'll
say it's a little smarter. But they been
out they've been out cooking. That's all
I'm going to say. They been out cooking.
So it ain't going nowhere for sure.
>> Yeah.
>> All right. Thanks, guys. Thank you.
Chris, nice to [music] meet you.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Hey, hey, hey.